bridgemanart.com 2019-03-20

# Privacy Policy

### This Privacy Policy may change from time to time, so please check it on a regular basis.

This Privacy Policy describes how Bridgeman Images ("Bridgeman" or "we" or "us") uses your personal data which we may collect on this website (current home page address: [www.bridgemanimages.com](http://www.bridgemanimages.com/)) ("Website") or which you may provide to us in connection with the Website. Please also read the Terms and Conditions of Use for details of how you may use the content contained in the Website and the extent of our responsibility for such content. You do not need to give us any personal data in order to browse the Website. If you do decide to register with us, or to contact us you may need to submit some personal data.

### What personal data do we collect about you?

We do not store or share credit card information. We collect from you limited personal data which includes your name(s), contact details and basic information about the company that you work for and possibly any other personal details that you provide to us, if this is necessary for us to deal with any questions you may send us. We will not ask you to send us any sensitive personal data, such as your religious convictions, state of mental or physical health, ethnic origin and similar sensitive information. Please do not send us any such personal data if possible to help us with our obligations under law. If you do send us such data, we will accept your explicit consent to use such sensitive personal data in the ways described in this Privacy Policy or as described by you.

### How do we collect your personal data?

We collect personal data from you when you complete the online registration process, which includes allocating your password for access to the Website and to use your Lightbox and account facilities. We also process your personal data every time that you contact us via email, post or telephone for the purposes of dealing with your query. We collect additional technical information automatically about use of our Website through cookies (see below).

### Why do we collect your personal information?

We use the information that we collect or that you provide to:

Give you access to the Website, by issuing you with a registered user identification.

To provide and manage the Lightbox facilities.

Respond to your questions.

Administer the Website and your use of the website.

### Use of cookies

We use cookies on our Website to help you browse it, and to allow us to authenticate your use of and to generally administer the Website. A cookie is a small text file stored on your hard drive containing information about you as the user, (some of which may be personal data, such as your name, location and registration information). Cookies are used in the general workings of the Website, but if you register, our cookies may be used to allow you to re-enter an area of the site in future without having to re-submit your registration details. Once you close your browser, most cookies will expire. If you are concerned about cookies, most browsers permit you to decline cookies. In most cases, you may refuse a cookie and still navigate our websites (although some functionality may be lost). You can find out more about cookies at [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/), an online public information resource provided by the Interactive Advertising Bureau UK, and if you have any particular concerns you can contact us at [info@bridgemanimages.com](mailto:info@bridgemanimages.com).

### Direct marketing

You have the option (via our registration form) to subscribe to our regular newsletter. If you choose to subscribe then you will send you our newsletter via email using the email address that you give us. If at any time you wish to stop receiving future newsletters, simply follow the link contained in the newsletter, or send a blank email to [unsubscribe@bridgemanimages.com](mailto:unsubscribe@bridgemanimages.com). We do not pass your personal data on to any third parties for direct marketing purposes, nor do we buy in lists of email addresses for our own direct marketing.

### Disclosure of your personal data to third parties

We will disclose your personal data to the following persons:

Our third party suppliers (in accordance with applicable data protection legislation) to allow them to carry out their services and fulfil your orders, including analytics providers such as Google Analytics and Intercom.

Any person who takes a transfer of our rights and obligations under any agreement we have with you.

Regulators (including the Office of the Information Commissioner), professional advisers to and agents of Bridgeman.

### Monitoring emails

Our network security system may automatically intercept or block any email you provide to us if the email contains any words or attachments that trigger the content filter to respond. The system is designed to detect and block potentially wrongful code or illicit or offensive content. It may exceptionally and by mistake block perfectly proper correspondence. You will be notified of such a block by return email. Please contact us on [info@bridgemanimages.com](mailto:info@bridgemanimages.com) if you need assistance.

### Links to other websites

This Privacy Policy does not cover links within the Website to websites of third parties. We are not responsible for the use of any personal data, including without limitation cookies, which you give directly to such third parties, or which they may collect about you while you visit pages hosted by them. Please refer to their respective privacy policies for information about their use of your personal data and their use of cookies.

### Access to the personal data we hold about you

You have the following rights over the personal data held about you:

. Right to access the data

. Right to rectification of inaccurate data

. Right to erasure ('right to be forgotten')

. Right to restriction of processing to verify accuracy of data

. Right to data portability

To view or update your profile, to see what data we hold and to correct any inaccurate data, please login and go to "My Bridgeman". 

To request your data to be erased, restricted or to submit a request for your data to be transferred to another data controller, please complete the enquiry form on the “Contact Us” page of the website.

We may need to contact you occasionally to ask that you confirm that the personal data that we hold about you is still accurate and up to date, to ensure that we continue to comply with our obligations under law.

### Data protection notification

Bridgeman Art Library Limited, 17-19 Garway Road, London, W2 4PH is registered in the United Kingdom with the Office of the Information Commissioner as a data controller. Our notification is filed under number Z8186788 and public access to our notification is generally available online through the following website: <https://ico.org.uk/>. This Privacy Policy was last updated on **24 May 2018**.

### Governing law

This Privacy Policy is governed by the laws of England and any dispute relating to this Privacy Policy and our data protection obligations will be resolved by the appropriate English supervisory authority (the Office of the Information Commissioner, [https://ico.org.uk](https://ico.org.uk/)/), or the English courts.

### Contacting us

We welcome your enquiries and comments on this Privacy Policy and any queries or concerns that you may have about the Website. Please contact us at [info@bridgemanimages.com](mailto:info@bridgemanimages.com) or by letter to the "Data Protection Officer" at Bridgeman Art Library Limited, 17-19 Garway Road, London, W2 4PH.
